I will talk to Ad Key and
today there will be a discussion with two big management people, first of all we will talk to Biocon's
CMD V Kalyan Rishabh
ji, after that there will be a conversation with Biocon's
person Kiran Mazumdar Shaw, the
discussion is going to be on the third quarter results only,
let's start with who all,
give you some information about the week,
its play was started in 1988 and this
company is in the business of container, copper transportation, it is the biggest player in the country
with 580, it has the biggest network in the country,
this company is facing the biggest problem in the export and domestic division business, please do that
to Ajay,
Ravi Kalyan Rishabh, Chairman and Managing Director of Pasha Company is associated, a
very warm welcome to Rawat Pradesh,
we have seen your numbers, they are looking quite good for the
third quarter, so first of all I would like to
know that the 20 percent
increase that you have shown in beta and in profit,
if you can break it down
for our videos, from where did you
see Bigg Boss, the growth in this voucher,
so see, we have brought some new scheme, one gym
in one gym  I was facing
problem of container availability
for exports. So after
looking at some reports, we
took advantage of the shipping line scheme of the port to the hinterland within India. We
brought a lot of containers to India and the
bottom cross doing see sports put
exporters help India and of held
business growth. So I was reading a little bit important from the closed side effect
also. I do
subscribe. 4,320
Business doing economic containers and
adding recent shopping app didi
products various types of products at her
boots got a good benefit in getting a job.
This dress got a lot of good from the
late to the
last which has
happened, if you
want, I will definitely
President Bhai Ji, I would like to talk to you further.
Tell us about the
growth seen in your domestic business, the growth has been
around 30%.
Volume certification is big in revenue. What kind
of source or have you reached the pre-quoted level?
What kind of effect did the quality reason have
on your business and this group
we are looking at, property 12 questions
What is this 12% due to? Have you added new
customers and volume? Has the volume been the
best? How did you stop it?
In domestic, you have increased the volume both
from existing customers and have
also added new customers. You have started this new loading
point, that is, nude pair, we
started it. We used to tell you
in an interview about this for the first time that there is
such
a point, it
joins from this point, we
call it directly,
we always do it in that, everything was
good, please subscribe to us,
like and subscribe, I came
to the North, came towards Delhi,
then took it from here, but in the West or
in the South, I brought it from the South to the Edit, I got South
West, something like that, I am doing acute belt,
that acute building is giving very good
profit and new circuit is being built,
so this is the existing customers
volume, new customers have been added
in Shakti building. Due to both these
reasons, we have got good growth in domestic
and will get it in future also. And in domestic, let me
tell you this thing here, we are starting a new thing,
normal cup.
Using this attack, we did it last year in 1984.
Now we are going to do it successfully for cement. In
the next financial year, the
general public is seeing growth in the cement business of
around 5 million to 10 million tonnes.
For that, we are buying containers.
New containers and new rakes are being received continuously. So, after
preparing all this, if we take up that new
business, then its volume will be 5
to 10 million tonnes. We can estimate it like this.
Today, we will do
12 million tonnes domestically in the entire year. We have done
9 million tonnes in just 9 months. So,
this is a fiber time in just 12 minutes
and you can understand what
growth will look like. The Great Indian Festival is a
correction. It looks very good
that your market position is also becoming positive
and its growth will also increase in the coming time. We will
talk about it in detail. Here,
you are looking at the market position, so
we have seen that your growth should be the
highest, as you said in the
quarter, but which  The entire industry could
not grow very fast, so
can you tell that you have played the market game
in this juice, you have done this
market game in this quarter, so like
draw different number of players, in the
rail movement that we do in December,
we have played the market game in it, some
markets are not interested in that in a pot,
in a market in which 30,
40, 50 km movement is done, people are
not interested in that,
we do that, we have to
fold it, in that our
market share has
increased from the last quarter, last year also, on
Thursday, it is
not much, we only press there,
we do cancer of the set coat, in that
we have gained a little from the market,
so thank you very much today, but today, V
Kalyan Ram ji, CMD, called here to join Swadesh and discuss with us on his number and on the company's plant,
telling us how Kabaddi has
grown, the BT cotton issue, the results have been
quite good, the market game has been played,
Ramkishore, the company is growing and at the same time  The
company is also entering into new types of business,
for this new containers are being purchased,
so the management of the company has shown that outlook
for now, but now we
will focus from Container Corporation on a sector
which is in news for the last several days and that is
IT, it was seen in the IT sector that
after the results of the three big companies, the decline in the party has increased a lot,
so why is there a decline,
why is there so much pressure on this sector and recovery
record can be seen in other sectors.